

susan vergnaud

Chicago, IL. 60608 • 773-459-3249

Education

Columbia College Chicago

•B.A. Interactive Arts & Media with a concentration in Graphic Design

Digital Bootcamp

• Web Development course

Design Lab

- •Interaction Design course
- Research & Strategy course

Summary

Creative designer and illustrator with experience in marketing, advertising and graphics. Currently responsible for planning, organizing and managing the design work-flow for various projects while working quickly, accurately, meeting tight deadlines and adhereing to brand consistency. I am dependable, self-motivated, and I have excellent communication / orginizational skills. I can work well independently and as part of a collaborative group. I have developed strong UI/UX skills through years of various design experience. I am continually expanding these skills through online courses.

Skills

Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, XD, Acrobat, Microsoft Office, Xcel, Dreamweaver, After Effects, Final Cut Pro, PowerPoint, Flash, HTML, CSS, Sketch.

Experience

City of Chicago 5/2013-Current

Graphic Artist III

Chicago, IL

- Design, create and complete art work for major exhibitions and or events.
- Conceptualize thematic designs for illustrations on various publication large displays and events.
- Create, develop and provide creative direction for various City departments projects.
- Manage the progress of multiple projects from initial conception to the final product.
- Manage, tag and archive project and photo assets that reside on various servers.

National Restaurant Assoc. Education Foundation Senior Graphic Designer Chicago, IL 1/2013-4/2013

- Designed, edited and laid out event marketing/signage, promotional posters, banners, emails, flyers and brochures for two events- Annual nationwide Invitational and the Annual golf classic event.
- Created various foundation and event logos for print and web use.
- Managed and tracked the progress of multiple projects and kept up with various editing rounds.
- Worked with the internal marketing communications team to revise and create all foundation materials regarding these two annual events.

Shared Marketing Services 1/2006-1/2013

Senior Graphic Designer

Chicago, IL

- Designed, edited and laid out web banners, emails, magazine ads, newsprint, brochures, promotional posters, postcards, logo design, flyers, icons, billboards.
- Created print, html templates and assests to be utilized for a mobile application.
- Conceptualized and designed a variety of print and web-related materials for local & national brands such as Audi USA/Canada, VW, BP, Harley Davidson, BP, New Balance, the Northface, Milgard and Ace Hardware.
- Edited animation, video, radio advertisements and created Photoshop website mockups.
- Proof print files before being sent out to outside vendors ensuring accuracy.
- Worked with account executives and the web dev. team to finish all the above tasks on time.

Interests

I like to draw, sketch, paint and do various freelance projects. I am also involved with the Taproot Foundation doing pro bono design work for non for profit organizations.

Portfolio Linkedin Email https://susanvergnaud.github.io | www.linkedin.com/in/susanvergnaud | susan.vergnaud@gmail.com